 Central dashboards to monitor entire renewable portfolio 
 Site dashboards for Plant KPIs 
 Equipment dashboards for Performance Enhancement (WMS, Inverters, Strings, Transformers, MFM &amp; Switchgears) 
 Display of parameter values and trends to get more insights on current condition/s 
 Choose your own Color Themes 
 Advanced Analytics Tools Library 
 Compare the ‘Best’ and ‘Worst’ performing devices 
 Diagnose the root cause of performance 
 Cross-Plant comparison of performance parameters 
 Export Analysis results to Third Party Software (e.g. Microsoft Power BI) 
 In-Built Reports Library 
 Customizable Report Views 
 Set Higher and Lower Value Range for parameters of all devices 
 Visualize and Categorize Parameter Values Effecting Performance 
 Variety of Supported Report Formats 
 Export Reports to Third Party Software (e.g. Microsoft Power BI) 
 Fast and Intuitive Plant Configuration 
 Support multiple and geographical assets through a common control center 
 Minimize downtime and maximize generations and profitability 
 Transform Raw data into valuable insights 
 Asset Management Software 
 Weather Forecasting Software 
 BI Reporting Tool 
 Cleaning Robot Integration 
 Tracker System Integration 
